MR. THEERAPONG PENGPIT (Nook)

IT Application Specialist, Lead programmer



091 989 5255



345/112 Moo.3 T.Surasak A.Sriracha Chonburi 20110



tpengpi@gmail.com



ABOUT

10 years' programmer work experience. Using C#, VB.Net, ASP.Net, MVC, .NET Core, Web API Restful, WCF Service, Bootstrap, Ajax, jQuery, JavaScript, Node.js, AngularJS, React, [PL/SQL, stored procedure], VB6, VBA, R, Python, Sisense, Microsoft Power BI and Microsoft Azure to success more 20 projects. Software Development Team Leader and Software Architecture

EXPERIENCE

IT Application Specialist | Celestica (Thailand) Limited, Chonburi Mar 2011 to present

- Software Development Team Leader and Software Architecture Design
- Crate Coding Standards, Define Project scope and Capability, R&D
- Cooperate, manage and achieved objectives 20 projects for Shop floor system control and Traceability
- Adaptive and predictive Analytics using R and Python
- Oversea project implementation in China, Mexico, and Canada
- Trained and mentored junior programmers in programming methodologies and best practices.

IT Officer | S.B.Maintenance Service CO., LTD |

Sep 2010 - Feb 2011 | 6 months

- Support for security policy, firewall, Network and Hardware
- Support windows 2003 server and windows 2008 server
- Development program for support company using VB 6.0, VB.NET

IT Development | Rajamangala University of Technology Tawam-Ok |

Mar 2010 - Aug 2010 | 6 months

- Development university's website by using language PHP, VB.NET and C#
- Support university's SQL Server 2003 data base system
- Support windows 2003 server

EDUCATION

2006-2010 Bachelor of Science (Computer Science), Rajamangala University of Technology Tawam-Ok

SKILL

DATABASE:

Oracle, SQL Server

MongoDB, DynamoDB

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE:

C#, VB.Net, ASP.Net, .NET Core, MVC ,Node.js, Bootstrap, Web API Restful, WCF Service, VB6 , Ajax, jQuery, JavaScript, [PL/SQL, stored procedure], VBA, Sisense (BI)

Python, R, Microsoft Power Bl

шшш

AngularJS, React

ШШШШ

Cloud Technology:

Microsoft Azure

11111111111

ENGLISH LANGUAGE

Listening |||||||

Speaking |||||

Reading | | | | | | | |